<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss
	xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0">
	<channel>
		<title>Audiobooks</title>
		<copyright></copyright>
		<itunes:subtitle></itunes:subtitle>
		<itunes:author></itunes:author>
		<itunes:summary></itunes:summary>
		<itunes:image href="https://am3pap003files.storage.live.com/y4m4F8W48sG6O8dER62hl8rM3Gb8ts0rLPqyzSLKs2SaNj4TVvqSih9QVGg0DIRSbdTzaqDLsElItu9ED07sLd5KOpoqCt3MgzEE13TDBjm9uNPrgXD_KmdTJeXn94ziKIc0A0gVbhbY5s6pQR-J6ughD2CJRPJJOi-dYbVW-RMyQAMVqV5oTerFaykh8NNlLKE?width=1400&amp;height=1400&amp;cropmode=none" />
		<itunes:category text="Technology"/>
		<item>
			<title>American Kingpin - The Epic Hunt for the Criminal Mastermind Behind the Silk Road</title>
			<itunes:author>Nick Bilton</itunes:author>
			<itunes:subtitle></itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>The unbelievable true story of the man who built a billion-dollar online drug empire from his bedroom - and almost got away with it

In 2011, a 26-year-old libertarian programmer named Ross Ulbricht launched the ultimate free market: the Silk Road, a clandestine website hosted on the Dark Web where anyone could trade anything - drugs, hacking software, forged passports, counterfeit cash, poisons - free of the government&#x27;s watchful eye.

It wasn&#x27;t long before the media got wind of the new website where anyone - not just teenagers and weed dealers but terrorists and black hat hackers - could buy and sell contraband detection-free. Spurred by a public outcry, the federal government launched an epic two-year manhunt for the site&#x27;s elusive proprietor, with no leads, no witnesses, and no clear jurisdiction. All the investigators knew was that whoever was running the site called himself the Dread Pirate Roberts.

The Silk Road quickly ballooned into a $1.2 billion enterprise, and Ross embraced his new role as kingpin. He enlisted a loyal crew of allies in high and low places, all as addicted to the danger and thrill of running an illegal marketplace as their customers were to the heroin they sold. Through his network he got wind of the target on his back and took drastic steps to protect himself - including ordering a hit on a former employee. As Ross made plans to disappear forever, the feds raced against the clock to catch a man they weren&#x27;t sure even existed, searching for a needle in the haystack of the global Internet.

Drawing on exclusive access to key players and two billion digital words and images Ross left behind, Vanity Fair correspondent and New York Times best-selling author Nick Bilton offers a tale filled with twists and turns, lucky breaks, and unbelievable close calls. It&#x27;s a story of the boy next door&#x27;s ambition gone criminal, spurred on by the clash between the new world of libertarian-leaning, anonymous, decentralized web advocates and the old world of government control, order, and the rule of law. Filled with unforgettable characters and capped by an astonishing climax, American Kingpin might be dismissed as too outrageous for fiction. But it&#x27;s all too real.</itunes:summary>
			<itunes:image href="https://am3pap003files.storage.live.com/y4mj3A9xQiNoaSfmFrbcs-kvG6Y5wYlVxVxIf7ihB_JJTh_7nedtSaZv8Lg1HgItThoGLmc8B7fc7FfwUFjJLWRxMi2IwlyVtEympah0Fns0Ivy5rvBb4p9p7h_EqKF03WMWugcQotDPI8GEEAZsvCiqeDblitp10YLgAldmkv4XAfXEHDsptoSU1nS4Y5Hzr10?width=2000&amp;height=2000&amp;cropmode=none" />
			<enclosure url="https://onedrive.live.com/download?resid=3455FE3FC4C110A5%219452&amp;authkey=!AJUz62UErYE8hFM&amp;filedisplay=track.m4a" length="351291416" type="audio/mpeg"/>
			<pubDate>Thu Mar 24 2022 11:53:57 GMT+0100 (Central European Standard Time)</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>44062</itunes:duration>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>A Burglar&#x27;s Guide to the City</title>
			<itunes:author>Geoff Manaugh</itunes:author>
			<itunes:subtitle></itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>Encompassing nearly 2,000 years of heists and tunnel jobs, break-ins and escapes, A Burglar&#x27;s Guide to the City offers an unexpected blueprint to the criminal possibilities in the world all around us. You&#x27;ll never see the city the same way again.

At the core of A Burglar&#x27;s Guide to the City is an unexpected and thrilling insight: how any building transforms when seen through the eyes of someone hoping to break into it. Studying architecture the way a burglar would, Geoff Manaugh takes listeners through walls, down elevator shafts, into panic rooms, up to the buried vaults of banks, and out across the rooftops of an unsuspecting city.

With the help of FBI special agents, reformed bank robbers, private security consultants, the LAPD Air Support Division, and architects past and present, the book dissects the built environment from both sides of the law. Whether picking padlocks or climbing the walls of high-rise apartments, finding gaps in a museum&#x27;s surveillance routine or discussing home invasions in ancient Rome, A Burglar&#x27;s Guide to the City has the tools, the tales, and the X-ray vision you need to see architecture as nothing more than an obstacle that can be outwitted and undercut.

Full of real-life heists both spectacular and absurd, A Burglar&#x27;s Guide to the City ensures that listeners will never enter a bank again without imagining how to loot the vault or walk down the street without planning the perfect getaway.</itunes:summary>
			<itunes:image href="https://am3pap003files.storage.live.com/y4mMRhhRwlmVHgpglhpK8rE3qzWPUeAmXR5gADnbZe-PgoQoNwgVucSoqtyL1e9ZMya3bSgu_LiszXujlfDmE4mfAorFNR02DGoHAvymA5RhnE5U0p4QF1GxLtlwiYYFUyMctyqSaWSJ_H7oFl_Ok84WtzWh1DGDjlkMWnTan5oZjhMj69OdiHLaGCU9Rb-gP7z?width=2000&amp;height=2000&amp;cropmode=none" />
			<enclosure url="https://onedrive.live.com/download?resid=3455FE3FC4C110A5%219449&amp;authkey=!ABLU9bG2iABCg_g&amp;filedisplay=track.m4a" length="236744063" type="audio/mpeg"/>
			<pubDate>Thu Mar 24 2022 11:53:57 GMT+0100 (Central European Standard Time)</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>28560</itunes:duration>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Bitcoin Billionaires - A True Story of Genius, Betrayal and Redemption</title>
			<itunes:author>Ben Mezrich</itunes:author>
			<itunes:subtitle></itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>Ben Mezrich&#x27;s 2009 best seller The Accidental Billionaires is the definitive account of Facebook&#x27;s founding - and the basis for the Academy Award-winning film The Social Network. Two of the story&#x27;s iconic characters are Harvard students Tyler and Cameron Winklevoss: identical twins, Olympic rowers, and legal foils to Mark Zuckerberg. Bitcoin Billionaires is the story of the brothers&#x27; redemption and revenge in the wake of their epic legal battle with Facebook - and the first great audiobook from the world of bitcoin. 

Planning to start careers as venture capitalists, the brothers quickly discover that no one will take their money for fear of alienating Zuckerberg. While nursing their wounds in Ibiza, they accidentally run into a shady character who tells them about a brand-new idea: cryptocurrency. 

Immersing themselves in what is then an obscure and sometimes sinister world, they begin to realise &#x27;crypto&#x27; is, in their own words, &#x27;either the next big thing or total bulls--t.&#x27; There&#x27;s nothing left to do but make a bet.  

From the Silk Road to the halls of the Securities and Exchange Commission to the Facebook boardroom, Bitcoin Billionaires will take us on a wild and surprising ride while illuminating a tantalising economic future. On November 26th, 2017, the Winklevoss brothers became the first bitcoin billionaires. Here&#x27;s the story of how they got there - as only Ben Mezrich could tell it.</itunes:summary>
			<itunes:image href="https://am3pap003files.storage.live.com/y4m0hbksslZn322gS5jIHmZKyhGOZSq9Kznh25dtIaGeTzA6PrYjPIgb_44ttqxIRqO1lM9FXF9CsgRQF2AntKLqdsrHZUHImkIODBq6a1AMyKsbgzlSMna4EDYDrudtRx_bfUilbZvfXqJ7iorMzNH_GdWvxaVXAUKQB5g1BmyRv139QCTrB4GBXkpcfaXXbb7?width=2000&amp;height=2000&amp;cropmode=none" />
			<enclosure url="https://onedrive.live.com/download?resid=3455FE3FC4C110A5%219453&amp;authkey=!ADrwRnPrhHLVgqg&amp;filedisplay=track.m4a" length="569654494" type="audio/mpeg"/>
			<pubDate>Thu Mar 24 2022 11:53:57 GMT+0100 (Central European Standard Time)</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>34320</itunes:duration>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Click Here to Kill Everybody - Security and Survival in a Hyper-connected World</title>
			<itunes:author>Bruce Schneier</itunes:author>
			<itunes:subtitle></itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>A world of &quot;smart&quot; devices means the Internet can kill people. We need to act. Now.

Everything is a computer. Ovens are computers that make things hot; refrigerators are computers that keep things cold. These computers - from home thermostats to chemical plants - are all online. The Internet, once a virtual abstraction, can now sense and touch the physical world.

As we open our lives to this future, often called the Internet of Things, we are beginning to see its enormous potential in ideas like driverless cars, smart cities, and personal agents equipped with their own behavioral algorithms. But every knife cuts two ways.

All computers can be hacked. And Internet-connected computers are the most vulnerable. Forget data theft: Cutting-edge digital attackers can now crash your car, your pacemaker, and the nation’s power grid. In Click Here to Kill Everybody, renowned expert and best-selling author Bruce Schneier examines the hidden risks of this new reality.

After exploring the full implications of a world populated by hyperconnected devices, Schneier reveals the hidden web of technical, political, and market forces that underpin the pervasive insecurities of today. He then offers common-sense choices for companies, governments, and individuals that can allow us to enjoy the benefits of this omnipotent age without falling prey to its vulnerabilities.

From principles for a more resilient Internet of Things to a recipe for sane government regulation and oversight to a better way to understand a truly new environment, Schneier’s vision is required listening for anyone invested in human flourishing.</itunes:summary>
			<itunes:image href="https://am3pap003files.storage.live.com/y4mw4xMET6_J3A4laINN9gPdZzrjt-idGA_wa9n3XSrpD_xQIXpYO3oNvwogLRmg3hvlFUTUU_iMIRqfq2DTBWNDxcK-HsVQ5U48-R4-rP-YQgRf_ZTkAP8CI3tDqRqCOpSa_Tjda78y0UYf721YNJ8f0dFXBO4RcO-4irA1u3ASww0fxFGcnQAvNa4i8IoBOnK?width=1921&amp;height=1920&amp;cropmode=none" />
			<enclosure url="https://onedrive.live.com/download?resid=3455FE3FC4C110A5%219451&amp;authkey=!AMVVjG-H7IzHiho&amp;filedisplay=track.m4a" length="233724099" type="audio/mpeg"/>
			<pubDate>Thu Mar 24 2022 11:53:57 GMT+0100 (Central European Standard Time)</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>29196</itunes:duration>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Code Girls - The Untold Story of the American Women Code Breakers of World War II</title>
			<itunes:author>Liza Mundy</itunes:author>
			<itunes:subtitle></itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>Recruited by the US Army and Navy from small towns and elite colleges, more than 10,000 women served as codebreakers during World War II. While their brothers and boyfriends took up arms, these women moved to Washington and learned the meticulous work of codebreaking. Their efforts shortened the war, saved countless lives, and gave them access to careers previously denied to them. A strict vow of secrecy nearly erased their efforts from history; now, through dazzling research and interviews with surviving code girls, best-selling author Liza Mundy brings to life this riveting and vital story of American courage, service, and scientific accomplishment.</itunes:summary>
			<itunes:image href="https://am3pap003files.storage.live.com/y4mK-nZrXASTEHQavkJQik5zrkHPJnC_VB3mdoetNky1rwYdyJUtM1ae5vXiTRahiKlBRl_FNtfUir6fD6GgTCGYiTUAhg-mwZEA2d-skVAIJpLtyGkd31E1b_j1nufV-DI9r1sZcXfFJbmBSASiK94eewCrtwEqZzDTQuqvfyw1beypD0V4s4OmEaNPSIlv-17?width=2000&amp;height=2000&amp;cropmode=none" />
			<enclosure url="https://onedrive.live.com/download?resid=3455FE3FC4C110A5%219454&amp;authkey=!AKJ4eIUzhxw3esA&amp;filedisplay=track.m4a" length="435285698" type="audio/mpeg"/>
			<pubDate>Thu Mar 24 2022 11:53:57 GMT+0100 (Central European Standard Time)</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>50678</itunes:duration>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Countdown to Zero Day - Stuxnet and the Launch of the World’s First Digital Weapon</title>
			<itunes:author>Kim Zetter</itunes:author>
			<itunes:subtitle></itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>Top cybersecurity journalist Kim Zetter tells the story behind the virus that sabotaged Iran’s nuclear efforts and shows how its existence has ushered in a new age of warfare - one in which a digital attack can have the same destructive capability as a megaton bomb.

In January 2010, inspectors with the International Atomic Energy Agency noticed that centrifuges at an Iranian uranium enrichment plant were failing at an unprecedented rate. The cause was a complete mystery - apparently as much to the technicians replacing the centrifuges as to the inspectors observing them.

Then, five months later, a seemingly unrelated event occurred: A computer security firm in Belarus was called in to troubleshoot some computers in Iran that were crashing and rebooting repeatedly.

At first, the firm’s programmers believed the malicious code on the machines was a simple, routine piece of malware. But as they and other experts around the world investigated, they discovered a mysterious virus of unparalleled complexity.

They had, they soon learned, stumbled upon the world’s first digital weapon. For Stuxnet, as it came to be known, was unlike any other virus or worm built before: Rather than simply hijacking targeted computers or stealing information from them, it escaped the digital realm to wreak actual, physical destruction on a nuclear facility.

In these pages, Wired journalist Kim Zetter draws on her extensive sources and expertise to tell the story behind Stuxnet’s planning, execution, and discovery, covering its genesis in the corridors of Bush’s White House and its unleashing on systems in Iran - and telling the spectacular, unlikely tale of the security geeks who managed to unravel a sabotage campaign years in the making.

But Countdown to Zero Day ranges far beyond Stuxnet itself.</itunes:summary>
			<itunes:image href="https://am3pap003files.storage.live.com/y4maAzNcjdv09Qb2yJJ4Std8ehGdL39C3izj25USlZ0qw3XdQb71PAn89ieSkydgQ9G01iCtJtK60CfK0bjiemAYaWdwCG0cbffb_Eg_viBvk9xQCJOd1N5a1EfH2B_RPPGByBSRBg96VEGhAuTUsGzhdpPF4UEGR_HlXPrc53-IXWFRmHzQc4ctrrETOUTNFRA?width=1800&amp;height=1800&amp;cropmode=none" />
			<enclosure url="https://onedrive.live.com/download?resid=3455FE3FC4C110A5%219455&amp;authkey=!AEb1T5p8OYBrB1Y&amp;filedisplay=track.m4a" length="391695910" type="audio/mpeg"/>
			<pubDate>Thu Mar 24 2022 11:53:57 GMT+0100 (Central European Standard Time)</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>46842</itunes:duration>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Cult of the Dead - Cow How the Original Hacking Supergroup Might Just Save the World</title>
			<itunes:author>Joseph Menn</itunes:author>
			<itunes:subtitle></itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>The shocking untold story of the elite secret society of hackers fighting to protect our privacy, our freedom - even democracy itself...

Cult of the Dead Cow is the tale of the oldest, most respected, and most famous American hacking group of all time. Though until now it has remained mostly anonymous, its members invented the concept of hacktivism, released the top tool for testing password security, and created what was for years the best technique for controlling computers from afar, forcing giant companies to work harder to protect customers. They contributed to the development of Tor, the most important privacy tool on the net, and helped build cyberweapons that advanced US security without injuring anyone. 

With its origins in the earliest days of the Internet, the cDc is full of oddball characters - activists, artists, even future politicians. Many of these hackers have become top executives and advisors walking the corridors of power in Washington and Silicon Valley. The most famous is former Texas Congressman and current presidential candidate Beto O&#x27;Rourke, whose time in the cDc set him up to found a tech business, launch an alternative publication in El Paso, and make long-shot bets on unconventional campaigns.

Today, the group and its followers are battling electoral misinformation, making personal data safer, and battling to keep technology a force for good instead of for surveillance and oppression. Cult of the Dead Cow shows how governments, corporations, and criminals came to hold immense power over individuals and how we can fight back against them.</itunes:summary>
			<itunes:image href="https://am3pap003files.storage.live.com/y4m4OXYbgrgoSAMuRIURNZAeqYUOOXYyakTgUL6dhKRoWgOaYu2OPB20TKOjMp3i0Y4_h7FOhaON87TZT2cGA4spn-tmrLhk7ooWJ6BflyLLYd8r6L4eCnhh8LYX6aZ13hRaQfdUTU49NBID4vY6jrYk_aTp_SPaTnSWYRbYsPtelCjbqZrSkU13ywVo9UoGTdl?width=500&amp;height=500&amp;cropmode=none" />
			<enclosure url="https://onedrive.live.com/download?resid=3455FE3FC4C110A5%219456&amp;authkey=!AIBWrF9hWTV3l9A&amp;filedisplay=track.m4a" length="247277095" type="audio/mpeg"/>
			<pubDate>Thu Mar 24 2022 11:53:57 GMT+0100 (Central European Standard Time)</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>29469</itunes:duration>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Dark Territory - The Secret History of Cyber War</title>
			<itunes:author>Fred Kaplan</itunes:author>
			<itunes:subtitle></itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>As cyber attacks dominate front-page news, as hackers join the list of global threats, and as top generals warn of a coming cyber war, few books are more timely and enlightening than Dark Territory: The Secret History of Cyber War by Slate columnist and Pulitzer Prize-winning journalist Fred Kaplan.

Kaplan probes the inner corridors of the National Security Agency, the beyond-top-secret cyber units in the Pentagon, the &quot;information warfare&quot; squads of the military services, and the national security debates in the White House to tell this never-before-told story of the officers, policymakers, scientists, and spies who devised this new form of warfare and who have been planning - and, more often than people know, fighting - these wars for decades.

From the 1991 Gulf War to conflicts in Haiti, Serbia, Syria, the former Soviet republics, Iraq, and Iran, where cyber warfare played a significant role, Dark Territory chronicles, in fascinating detail, an unknown past that shines an unsettling light on our future.</itunes:summary>
			<itunes:image href="https://am3pap003files.storage.live.com/y4mYuZ1yvIgEXpNMNvWr5UzRLwqMdXkY4KrvwXCwrXoA5NTp7c_kMIsdQmifIL-jNd_n1Zm2kspdSk5VT3joJHluhAbMd8Ff0H2bfTbS-_97d6wKguLZ1zIrQzwIaciBvIkLKgjUOXxfGl3K55JQzNO-T0nKmXc5SLO0ZlWK1cvsMHgcFpjxwQNCuZ00ElfFhrn?width=2000&amp;height=2000&amp;cropmode=none" />
			<enclosure url="https://onedrive.live.com/download?resid=3455FE3FC4C110A5%219433&amp;authkey=!ANkAD8LnEpB3uI4&amp;filedisplay=track.m4a" length="267475119" type="audio/mpeg"/>
			<pubDate>Thu Mar 24 2022 11:53:57 GMT+0100 (Central European Standard Time)</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>32550</itunes:duration>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Data and Goliath - The Hidden Battles to Capture Your Data and Control Your World</title>
			<itunes:author>Bruce Schneier</itunes:author>
			<itunes:subtitle></itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>Data is everywhere. We create it every time we go online, turn our phones on (or off), and pay with credit cards. The data is stored, studied, and bought and sold by corporations and governments for surveillance and for control. &quot;Foremost security expert&quot; (Wired) and best-selling author Bruce Schneier shows how this data has led to a double-edged Internet - a Web that gives power to the people but is abused by the institutions on which those people depend.

In Data and Goliath, Schneier reveals the full extent of surveillance, censorship, and propaganda in society today, examining the risks of cybercrime, cyberterrorism, and cyberwar. He shares technological, legal, and social solutions that can help shape a more equal, private, and secure world. This is an audiobook to which everyone with an Internet connection - or bank account or smart device or car, for that matter - needs to listen.</itunes:summary>
			<itunes:image href="https://am3pap003files.storage.live.com/y4m1oQ4rEC71urAOvelcL4whT83KlFGlI9KMyCmNcEJkch53T-rGjTtaHVReGxv-srsJ-XuEqna-NdXxEeu03aB7rJv0vbpKPQyLXlg4vHNKzj4deMFGJNomJU3iTkJvAt1reF-KfWu6NtNG523iyki_CkHvF0Z9kMEBMmgbCH6BktZPP0D8lzBAxai7v-hEYw0?width=2000&amp;height=2000&amp;cropmode=none" />
			<enclosure url="https://onedrive.live.com/download?resid=3455FE3FC4C110A5%219434&amp;authkey=!AE_YVpuZQP2w0IY&amp;filedisplay=track.m4a" length="287267660" type="audio/mpeg"/>
			<pubDate>Thu Mar 24 2022 11:53:57 GMT+0100 (Central European Standard Time)</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>33978</itunes:duration>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Dawn of the Code War - America’s Battle Against Russia, China, and the Rising Global Cyber Threat</title>
			<itunes:author>Garrett Graff and John P. Carlin</itunes:author>
			<itunes:subtitle></itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>The inside story of how America&#x27;s enemies launched a cyberwar against us - and how we&#x27;ve learned to fight back.

With each passing year, the Internet-linked attacks on America&#x27;s interests have grown in both frequency and severity. Overmatched by our military, countries like North Korea, China, Iran, and Russia have found us vulnerable in cyberspace. The &quot;Code War&quot; is upon us. 

In this dramatic audiobook, former assistant attorney general John P. Carlin takes listeners to the front lines of a global but little-understood fight as the Justice Department and the FBI chases down hackers, online terrorist recruiters, and spies. Today, as our entire economy goes digital, from banking to manufacturing to transportation, the potential targets for our enemies multiply. 

This firsthand account is both a remarkable untold story and a warning of dangers yet to come.</itunes:summary>
			<itunes:image href="https://am3pap003files.storage.live.com/y4mMsbK70rD_Pvop8xRupCyi2agiKKW6I0BzKfiEHudNtnS79_qETqIxYTBOBq2pDzOuRwXvovxZfqqY2mQBEWm-k-AU8RINdkGVR0jqdtX1i91ai8e8ct1S-r5IKjriYCJrhHc_xKVJABwoI0gmMCi7OYWCECuzRmfSXHapfqJn2IyL3Fy4n4jc2jtSdbpoSpw?width=2000&amp;height=2000&amp;cropmode=none" />
			<enclosure url="https://onedrive.live.com/download?resid=3455FE3FC4C110A5%219435&amp;authkey=!AMYddDfhKkbcMGI&amp;filedisplay=track.m4a" length="292469169" type="audio/mpeg"/>
			<pubDate>Thu Mar 24 2022 11:53:57 GMT+0100 (Central European Standard Time)</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>61159</itunes:duration>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Fatal System Error - The Hunt for the New Crime Lords Who Are Bringing Down the Internet</title>
			<itunes:author>Joseph Menn</itunes:author>
			<itunes:subtitle></itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>In this disquieting cyber thriller, Joseph Menn takes readers into the murky hacker underground, traveling the globe from San Francisco to Costa Rica and London to Russia. His guides are California surfer and computer whiz Barrett Lyon and a fearless British high-tech agent. Through these heroes, Menn shows the evolution of cyber-crime from small-time thieving to sophisticated, organized gangs, who began by attacking corporate websites but increasingly steal financial data from consumers and defense secrets from governments. Using unprecedented access to Mob businesses and Russian officials, the book reveals how top criminals earned protection from the Russian government.

Fatal System Error penetrates both the Russian cyber-mob and La Cosa Nostra as the two fight over the Internet&#x27;s massive spoils. The cloak-and-dagger adventure shows why cyber-crime is much worse than you thought and why the Internet might not survive.</itunes:summary>
			<itunes:image href="https://am3pap003files.storage.live.com/y4momz5QMltD3D1uGKAZZSXPa2fB43BWpRgVpJU6zAyDerzyRkkQf6k0nn-uj_mUbLOGEGKsLWZBIF9FbpRz3C0ZEjhcql6TUj5I1m5LjQm45OkM_M_7NIIratS4mj3q6BvWZr37WnUjaEZ7ArQomcg6515E6c00AxMCWXV5hqjROywfJ2Y7mcOBjYAOSn7X0ij?width=500&amp;height=500&amp;cropmode=none" />
			<enclosure url="https://onedrive.live.com/download?resid=3455FE3FC4C110A5%219436&amp;authkey=!AKMCd9Im0kUT9wE&amp;filedisplay=track.m4a" length="239939899" type="audio/mpeg"/>
			<pubDate>Thu Mar 24 2022 11:53:57 GMT+0100 (Central European Standard Time)</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>30187</itunes:duration>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Future Crimes - Everything Is Connected, Everyone Is Vulnerable and What We Can Do About It</title>
			<itunes:author>Marc Goodman</itunes:author>
			<itunes:subtitle></itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>One of the world&#x27;s leading authorities on global security, Marc Goodman takes listeners deep into the digital underground to expose the alarming ways criminals, corporations, and even countries are using new and emerging technologies against you - and how this makes everyone more vulnerable than ever imagined.

Technological advances have benefited our world in immeasurable ways, but there is an ominous flip side: Our technology can be turned against us. Hackers can activate baby monitors to spy on families, thieves are analyzing social media posts to plot home invasions, and stalkers are exploiting the GPS on smart phones to track their victims&#x27; every move. We all know today&#x27;s criminals can steal identities, drain online bank accounts, and wipe out computer servers, but that&#x27;s just the beginning. To date, no computer has been created that could not be hacked - a sobering fact given our radical dependence on these machines for everything from our nation&#x27;s power grid to air traffic control to financial services.

Yet, as ubiquitous as technology seems today, just over the horizon is a tidal wave of scientific progress that will leave our heads spinning. If today&#x27;s Internet is the size of a golf ball, tomorrow&#x27;s will be the size of the sun. Welcome to the Internet of Things, a living, breathing, global information grid where every physical object will be online. But with greater connections come greater risks. Implantable medical devices such as pacemakers can be hacked to deliver a lethal jolt of electricity and a car&#x27;s brakes can be disabled at high speed from miles away. Meanwhile, 3-D printers can produce AK-47s, bioterrorists can download the recipe for Spanish flu, and cartels are using fleets of drones to ferry drugs across borders.

With explosive insights based upon a career in law enforcement and counterterrorism, Marc Goodman takes listeners on a vivid journey through the darkest recesses of the Internet.</itunes:summary>
			<itunes:image href="https://am3pap003files.storage.live.com/y4myg15uvTrgBCQl88dHI3SULwQ3nKjw2uUxQuJo2uN_XdI1fUgAEV7LDcpWIgwF-MT_A6pTWD-9BYclG527qb01A9gsXxJGmo0cGhH19ECrxxVLwilr59F-mFT6QO4ggNZo8P9M2ZzDjQSPBQpbcib1zX_h6FnUt_fWVGkV2qQj2Hq8ELz1anShjLCF24OMIRF?width=2000&amp;height=2000&amp;cropmode=none" />
			<enclosure url="https://onedrive.live.com/download?resid=3455FE3FC4C110A5%219438&amp;authkey=!APAqSLd9okjreRo&amp;filedisplay=track.m4a" length="576826342" type="audio/mpeg"/>
			<pubDate>Thu Mar 24 2022 11:53:57 GMT+0100 (Central European Standard Time)</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>72595</itunes:duration>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Ghost in the Wires - My Adventures as the World’s Most Wanted Hacker</title>
			<itunes:author>Kevin Mitnick and William L. Simon</itunes:author>
			<itunes:subtitle></itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>Kevin Mitnick was the most elusive computer break-in artist in history. He accessed computers and networks at the world’s biggest companies—and however fast the authorities were, Mitnick was faster, sprinting through phone switches, computer systems, and cellular networks. He spent years skipping through cyberspace, always three steps ahead and labeled unstoppable. But for Kevin, hacking wasn’t just about technological feats—it was an old fashioned confidence game that required guile and deception to trick the unwitting out of valuable information.

Driven by a powerful urge to accomplish the impossible, Mitnick bypassed security systems and blazed into major organizations including Motorola, Sun Microsystems, and Pacific Bell. But as the FBI’s net began to tighten, Kevin went on the run, engaging in an increasingly sophisticated cat-and-mouse game that led through false identities, a host of cities, plenty of close shaves, and to an ultimate showdown with the feds, who would stop at nothing to bring him down.

Ghost in the Wires is a thrilling true story of intrigue, suspense, and unbelievable escape and a portrait of a visionary whose creativity, skills, and persistence forced the authorities to rethink the way they pursued him, inspiring ripples that brought permanent changes in the way people and companies protect their most sensitive information.</itunes:summary>
			<itunes:image href="https://am3pap003files.storage.live.com/y4mGqBzWelHWRev9z7Z_gk-DcU8mZ_Q5LiL0JzodS9hM_pSWj7fZPIA76KKlDH3e7Aa2aNRzxJNVL8PdJcGrYy14Y0ZybNdimUtcFx1k1M2FFVniLH86-4Z14CoyhE1GPhzAuuqQbo9KDUm2wo5yxH6TCLJ625aJS21FvZesb8s_cK00oi_-etvIQ-0by48EFTD?width=2000&amp;height=2000&amp;cropmode=none" />
			<enclosure url="https://onedrive.live.com/download?resid=3455FE3FC4C110A5%219437&amp;authkey=!AACS5-2nfF6djiA&amp;filedisplay=track.m4a" length="416023492" type="audio/mpeg"/>
			<pubDate>Thu Mar 24 2022 11:53:57 GMT+0100 (Central European Standard Time)</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>50486</itunes:duration>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Hackers - Heroes of the Computer Revolution 25th Anniversary Edition</title>
			<itunes:author>Steven Levy</itunes:author>
			<itunes:subtitle></itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>Steven Levy&#x27;s classic book traces the exploits of the computer revolution&#x27;s original hackers - those brilliant and eccentric nerds from the late 1950s through the early &#x27;80s who took risks, bent the rules, and pushed the world in a radical new direction. With updated material from noteworthy hackers such as Bill Gates, Mark Zuckerberg, Richard Stallman, and Steve Wozniak, Hackers is a fascinating story that begins in early computer research labs and leads to the first home computers.

Levy profiles the imaginative brainiacs who found clever and unorthodox solutions to computer engineering problems. They had a shared sense of values, known as &quot;the hacker ethic&quot; that still thrives today. Hackers captures a seminal period in recent history when underground activities blazed a trail for today&#x27;s digital world, from MIT students finagling access to clunky computer-card machines to the DIY culture that spawned the Altair and the Apple II.</itunes:summary>
			<itunes:image href="https://am3pap003files.storage.live.com/y4m7DrIeAwfTVmgSjCEq2t0IlC7dx2daHYP7kAdxKBLBwdKNx979H1KVAbLXgqT8D-s19aWtzsCpeSx9b9NlW4YgJZyNB4C8EiDTyGPqMbiK6FoK_Gi_tw3WrEcXMURoapq1QjxhZILja5G-HaCh2JbZqIZDStyKB_rI4HZWYyZi4YVMSARhpTWzm0AfBi1TFk5?width=2000&amp;height=2000&amp;cropmode=none" />
			<enclosure url="https://onedrive.live.com/download?resid=3455FE3FC4C110A5%219442&amp;authkey=!AHdz9IutA6SqmDE&amp;filedisplay=track.m4a" length="1005783727" type="audio/mpeg"/>
			<pubDate>Thu Mar 24 2022 11:53:57 GMT+0100 (Central European Standard Time)</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>73453</itunes:duration>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Kingpin - How One Hacker Took Over the Billion-Dollar Cybercrime Underground</title>
			<itunes:author>Kevin Poulsen</itunes:author>
			<itunes:subtitle></itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>The word spread through the hacking underground like some unstoppable new virus: Someone - some brilliant, audacious crook - had just staged a hostile takeover of an online criminal network that siphoned billions of dollars from the U.S. economy. The FBI rushed to launch an ambitious undercover operation aimed at tracking down this new kingpin. Other agencies around the world deployed dozens of moles and double agents.

Together, the cybercops lured numerous unsuspecting hackers into their clutches. Yet at every turn, their main quarry displayed an uncanny ability to sniff out their snitches and see through their plots. The culprit they sought was the most unlikely of criminals: a brilliant programmer with a hippie ethic and a supervillain&#x27;s double identity. Together with a smooth-talking con artist, he ran a massive real-world crime ring.</itunes:summary>
			<itunes:image href="https://am3pap003files.storage.live.com/y4m_f9PRPb8ZLxZKL4gdwJsnPU-xYzbG8vmQPbyrQfpXzhyErOmcXFn9-4LVnGOWZnriExijqbxiYQMzGkdA6FdZN5pgW1LfTOj33N_IBvIEQxRXOxNTu0AOYDE6KV3GxVid-JvBXBWCUqTkDr5pQM5fJUJJkyxaYqSYyGIRYER9QOMCVdl63nrtqTlLTAsM2-b?width=2000&amp;height=2000&amp;cropmode=none" />
			<enclosure url="https://onedrive.live.com/download?resid=3455FE3FC4C110A5%219439&amp;authkey=!AG3cBYYMPm7E5Sg&amp;filedisplay=track.m4a" length="421634960" type="audio/mpeg"/>
			<pubDate>Thu Mar 24 2022 11:53:57 GMT+0100 (Central European Standard Time)</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>29330</itunes:duration>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>LikeWar - The Weaponization of Social Media</title>
			<itunes:author>Emerson T. Brooking and P. W. Singer</itunes:author>
			<itunes:subtitle></itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>Two defense experts explore the collision of war, politics, and social media, where the most important battles are now only a click away.

Through the weaponization of social media, the Internet is changing war and politics, just as war and politics are changing the Internet. Terrorists livestream their attacks, “Twitter wars” produce real world casualties, and viral misinformation alters not just the result of battles, but the very fate of nations. The result is that war, tech, and politics have blurred into a new kind of battlespace that plays out on our smartphones.

P. W. Singer and Emerson Brooking tackle the mind bending questions that arise when war goes online and the online world goes to war. They explore how ISIS copies the Instagram tactics of Taylor Swift, a former World of Warcraft addict foils war crimes thousands of miles away, Internet trolls shape elections, and China uses a smartphone app to police the thoughts of 1.4 billion citizens. What can be kept secret in a world of networks? Does social media expose the truth or bury it? And what role do ordinary people now play in international conflicts?

Delving into the web’s darkest corners, we meet the unexpected warriors of social media, such as the rapper turned jihadist PR czar and the Russian hipsters who wage unceasing infowars against the West. Finally, looking to the crucial years ahead, LikeWar outlines a radical new paradigm for understanding and defending against the unprecedented threats of our networked world.</itunes:summary>
			<itunes:image href="https://am3pap003files.storage.live.com/y4mxEYJh7sWTOf3MhGNfa6YVxw6HsVMbcqDGec4YBeOKQEsDD5o_4orjPUNZFbYI3YoJ8dd4NfL8K7DEcOHH3Ezrdzi3526GpWLxNhM1zIebJkSbIwRLYio999U8jf1ws23IcRsGUv5RGSZfUaNkqGr3t8k-4xb_6eArmMaQQdVNLBebkerIJkNTd_ImQE8vrO8?width=2000&amp;height=2000&amp;cropmode=none" />
			<enclosure url="https://onedrive.live.com/download?resid=3455FE3FC4C110A5%219440&amp;authkey=!AGxFODAot14RF70&amp;filedisplay=track.m4a" length="326954640" type="audio/mpeg"/>
			<pubDate>Thu Mar 24 2022 11:53:57 GMT+0100 (Central European Standard Time)</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>40870</itunes:duration>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Little Brother</title>
			<itunes:author>Cory Doctorow</itunes:author>
			<itunes:subtitle></itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>Marcus, a.k.a “w1n5t0n,” is only seventeen years old, but he figures he already knows how the system works–and how to work the system. Smart, fast, and wise to the ways of the networked world, he has no trouble outwitting his high school’s intrusive but clumsy surveillance systems.

But his whole world changes when he and his friends find themselves caught in the aftermath of a major terrorist attack on San Francisco. In the wrong place at the wrong time, Marcus and his crew are apprehended by the Department of Homeland Security and whisked away to a secret prison where they’re mercilessly interrogated for days.

When the DHS finally releases them, Marcus discovers that his city has become a police state where every citizen is treated like a potential terrorist. He knows that no one will believe his story, which leaves him only one option: to take down the DHS himself.</itunes:summary>
			<itunes:image href="https://am3pap003files.storage.live.com/y4mDtOx53QVaokuH4ZuYJ1YYR8cELig2_aKo2Y7rUVl2xlh5WSj1I4J7756nTHkZra-zCsMNpdjb-KkFR4Unu6X9JmnRcbaorjyRd7EM9_Sfsz7BGHU2oNgKlZpcHczJPxDYL-Wl7VAONAJ7hTrGDIjSekYJ59NoZZhq9xwU3VCUrwh3IhTIzWg4vDUUdgKFW3r?width=1536&amp;height=1536&amp;cropmode=none" />
			<enclosure url="https://onedrive.live.com/download?resid=3455FE3FC4C110A5%219441&amp;authkey=!AP5sZMq0DmA_ULU&amp;filedisplay=track.m4a" length="193051975" type="audio/mpeg"/>
			<pubDate>Thu Mar 24 2022 11:53:57 GMT+0100 (Central European Standard Time)</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>42871</itunes:duration>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Sandworm - A New Era of Cyberwar and the Hunt for the Kremlin’s Most Dangerous Hackers</title>
			<itunes:author>Andy Greenberg</itunes:author>
			<itunes:subtitle></itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>From Wired senior writer Andy Greenberg comes the true story of the most devastating cyberattack in history and the desperate hunt to identify and track the elite Russian agents behind it.

&quot;Much more than a true-life techno-thriller...a tour through a realm that is both invisible and critical to the daily lives of every person alive in the 21st century.&quot; (Los Angeles Times)

In 2014, the world witnessed the start of a mysterious series of cyberattacks. Targeting American utility companies, NATO, and electric grids in Eastern Europe, the strikes grew ever more brazen. They culminated in the summer of 2017, when the malware known as NotPetya was unleashed, penetrating, disrupting, and paralyzing some of the world&#x27;s largest businesses - from drug manufacturers to software developers to shipping companies. At the attack&#x27;s epicenter in Ukraine, ATMs froze. The railway and postal systems shut down. Hospitals went dark. NotPetya spread around the world, inflicting an unprecedented 10 billion dollars in damage - the largest, most devastating cyberattack the world had ever seen.

The hackers behind these attacks are quickly gaining a reputation as the most dangerous team of cyberwarriors in history: a group known as Sandworm. Working in the service of Russia&#x27;s military intelligence agency, they represent a persistent, highly skilled force, one whose talents are matched by their willingness to launch broad, unrestrained attacks on the most critical infrastructure of their adversaries. They target government and private sector, military, and civilians alike.

A chilling, globe-spanning detective story, Sandworm considers the danger this force poses to our national security and stability. As the Kremlin&#x27;s role in foreign government manipulation comes into greater focus, Sandworm exposes the realities not just of Russia&#x27;s global digital offensive, but of an era where warfare ceases to be waged on the battlefield. It reveals how the lines between digital and physical conflict, between wartime and peacetime, have begun to blur - with world-shaking implications.</itunes:summary>
			<itunes:image href="https://am3pap003files.storage.live.com/y4mjTxoNa_C-qsK-k5GG8mbgD_HCQZVvkGnVc95Jh-Owtp1vSIKBcOJitmNjZVMJANzY5ZOscQT4UtkFT_q4RobCUC8EyqpcEHiJMvyiH1ZqGEEaVllRVS6NQWtgZZlSjSaiPy5-WyYSs_8-kQFzg4Ht_uzuJ1EI4Q95vCDAg7tBb9C4rYGRpSzBV-mDyWQim-p?width=1998&amp;height=2000&amp;cropmode=none" />
			<enclosure url="https://onedrive.live.com/download?resid=3455FE3FC4C110A5%219444&amp;authkey=!AMCbqxCJdBWMp9s&amp;filedisplay=track.m4a" length="672006330" type="audio/mpeg"/>
			<pubDate>Thu Mar 24 2022 11:53:57 GMT+0100 (Central European Standard Time)</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>43349</itunes:duration>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Spam Nation - The Inside Story of Organized Cybercrime – from Global Epidemic to Your Front Door</title>
			<itunes:author>Brian Krebs</itunes:author>
			<itunes:subtitle></itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>There is a Threat Lurking Online with the Power to Destroy Your Finances, Steal Your Personal Data, and Endanger Your Life.

In Spam Nation, investigative journalist and cybersecurity expert Brian Krebs unmasks the criminal masterminds driving some of the biggest spam and hacker operations targeting Americans and their bank accounts. Tracing the rise, fall, and alarming resurrection of the digital mafia behind the two largest spam pharmacies - and countless viruses, phishing, and spyware attacks - he delivers the first definitive narrative of the global spam problem and its threat to consumers everywhere.</itunes:summary>
			<itunes:image href="https://am3pap003files.storage.live.com/y4mruTFgRXR7eV4iaredJumxovcOXrxhNm-8fxMOzEfIP-YZw4rQM7LHT5MNaGPOYm4PBxpZC2IVkWXYOZx7IMHF_n18wOnMYi7ANlaCAc0G75lNasKnqsIldDsJdQefMjyFe2uuqNIQaqxemd5OPzUsgqLpqBvDbDlAhSI5J4pT9pkSX1IpZwuHcn6A73DQhHs?width=2000&amp;height=2000&amp;cropmode=none" />
			<enclosure url="https://onedrive.live.com/download?resid=3455FE3FC4C110A5%219443&amp;authkey=!AGDBaUnfN_w5_vk&amp;filedisplay=track.m4a" length="261502091" type="audio/mpeg"/>
			<pubDate>Thu Mar 24 2022 11:53:57 GMT+0100 (Central European Standard Time)</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>31588</itunes:duration>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>The Cuckoo’s Egg - Tracking a Spy Through the Maze of Computer Espionage</title>
			<itunes:author>Clifford Stoll</itunes:author>
			<itunes:subtitle></itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>Bloomsbury presents This Is How They Tell Me the World Ends by Nicole Perlroth, read by Allyson Ryan.

Zero day: a software bug that allows a hacker to break into your devices and move around undetected. One of the most coveted tools in a spy&#x27;s arsenal, a zero day has the power to silently spy on your iPhone, dismantle the safety controls at a chemical plant, alter an election and shut down the electric grid (just ask Ukraine).

For decades, under cover of classification levels and non-disclosure agreements, the United States government became the world’s dominant hoarder of zero days. US government agents paid top dollar - first thousands and later millions of dollars - to hackers willing to sell their lock-picking code and their silence.

Then the United States lost control of its hoard and the market.

Now those zero days are in the hands of hostile nations and mercenaries who do not care if your vote goes missing, your clean water is contaminated or our nuclear plants melt down.

Filled with spies, hackers, arms dealers and a few unsung heroes, written like a thriller and a reference, This Is How They Tell Me the World Ends is an astonishing feat of journalism. Based on years of reporting and hundreds of interviews, The New York Times reporter Nicole Perlroth lifts the curtain on a market in shadow, revealing the urgent threat faced by us all if we cannot bring the global cyber arms race to heel.</itunes:summary>
			<itunes:image href="https://am3pap003files.storage.live.com/y4mTsltcyanjcnZH6zjMQWmqKVFDYjZVX1jP-U6VZsr8nEIVQujaeG3OmZQjbNJJ229vEXL5p5dGmbB5IWiBgdPgsmUQ-otQx7QRdZRS6R_Y5Mnj3XNgSRHe252ZnuFPmw4AQeP5Q7bfe4eoYLtm_4f6hv9r24anf2Od1mdt9HulQTy5j7aqKys0iKWvQZWo1Bw?width=2000&amp;height=2000&amp;cropmode=none" />
			<enclosure url="https://onedrive.live.com/download?resid=3455FE3FC4C110A5%219446&amp;authkey=!ABXi3oaRUoqKrNw&amp;filedisplay=track.m4a" length="749414975" type="audio/mpeg"/>
			<pubDate>Thu Mar 24 2022 11:53:57 GMT+0100 (Central European Standard Time)</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>45997</itunes:duration>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>The Hacker Crackdown - Law and Disorder on the Electronic Frontier</title>
			<itunes:author>Bruce Sterling</itunes:author>
			<itunes:subtitle></itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>The bestselling cyberpunk author “has produced by far the most stylish report from the computer outlaw culture since Steven Levy’s Hackers” (Publishers Weekly).

Bruce Sterling delves into the world of high-tech crime and punishment in one of the first books to explore the cyberspace breaches that threaten national security. From the crash of AT&amp;T’s long-distance switching system to corporate cyberattacks, he investigates government and law enforcement efforts to break the back of America’s electronic underground in the 1990s. In this modern classic, “Sterling makes the hackers - who live in the ether between terminals under noms de net such as VaxCat - as vivid as Wyatt Earp and Doc Holliday. His book goes a long way towards explaining the emerging digital world and its ethos” (Publishers Weekly).

This edition features a new preface by the author that analyzes the sobering increase in computer crime over the twenty-five years since The Hacker Crackdown was first published.

“Offbeat and brilliant.” - Booklist

“Thoroughly researched, this account of the government’s crackdown on the nebulous but growing computer-underground provides a thoughtful report on the laws and rights being defined on the virtual frontier of cyberspace . . . . An enjoyable, informative, and (as the first mainstream treatment of the subject) potentially important book . . . Sterling is a fine and knowledgeable guide to this strange new world.” - Kirkus Reviews

“A well-balanced look at this new group of civil libertarians. Written with humor and intelligence, this book is highly recommended.” - Library Journal</itunes:summary>
			<itunes:image href="https://am3pap003files.storage.live.com/y4m-s4muF0WVRci3qpuq6tQczZxBfHQkZz1It60GRBtx6LwkjJaPFAO2FdaLPd3_Sbl1YJoBpcRwIdjkFz6F0Rs1l05P8sMN9TzEu3QkZ3HGEPRGRxamT95YoTIwlN9mDbip0jJBYpJkmHewSh42lvxOst80CS8GXN-Lg4eKwHB0W2xl1QGdj8UCbmQJd_eH0r8?width=2000&amp;height=2000&amp;cropmode=none" />
			<enclosure url="https://onedrive.live.com/download?resid=3455FE3FC4C110A5%219447&amp;authkey=!AGGVK4J0PCGl0J0&amp;filedisplay=track.m4a" length="839167543" type="audio/mpeg"/>
			<pubDate>Thu Mar 24 2022 11:53:57 GMT+0100 (Central European Standard Time)</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>46491</itunes:duration>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>The Perfect Weapon - War, Sabotage, and Fear in the Cyber Age</title>
			<itunes:author>David E. Sanger</itunes:author>
			<itunes:subtitle></itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>Soon to be an HBO® documentary from award-winning director John Maggio

“An important - and deeply sobering - new book about cyberwarfare.” (Nicholas Kristof, New York Times)

The Perfect Weapon is the startling inside story of how the rise of cyberweapons transformed geopolitics like nothing since the invention of the atomic bomb. Cheap to acquire, easy to deny, and usable for a variety of malicious purposes, cyber is now the weapon of choice for democracies, dictators, and terrorists. Two presidents - Bush and Obama - drew first blood with Operation Olympic Games, which used malicious code to blow up Iran’s nuclear centrifuges, and yet America proved remarkably unprepared when its own weapons were stolen from its arsenal and, during President Trump’s first year, turned back on the United States and its allies. And if Obama would begin his presidency by helping to launch the new era of cyberwar, he would end it struggling unsuccessfully to defend against Russia’s broad attack on the 2016 US election.

Moving from the White House Situation Room to the dens of Chinese government hackers to the boardrooms of Silicon Valley, New York Times national security correspondent David Sanger reveals a world coming face-to-face with the perils of technological revolution, where everyone is a target.

“Timely and bracing.... With the deep knowledge and bright clarity that have long characterized his work, Sanger recounts the cunning and dangerous development of cyberspace into the global battlefield of the 21st century.” (Washington Post)</itunes:summary>
			<itunes:image href="https://am3pap003files.storage.live.com/y4mPiEDXh-wIAKR7bHaRJ_miaJV7dX6rhYF7pdChWdlIj2LBvLX-Ld97Vf_0BthPR8KM7zqGIYOv2XpZ_s1oiV1gJFrMmghrPFQT5CJRWUyMO-imeD5NA62_bsr4FrPPX5GIzjl6yqRNu3afdTh3qdHfkUgGBUM1Xv-yvF32_VfcKFEx1jzX0E_3hjibmX1aJM5?width=1650&amp;height=1650&amp;cropmode=none" />
			<enclosure url="https://onedrive.live.com/download?resid=3455FE3FC4C110A5%219445&amp;authkey=!AFwmZzH7x1s4H54&amp;filedisplay=track.m4a" length="358929416" type="audio/mpeg"/>
			<pubDate>Thu Mar 24 2022 11:53:57 GMT+0100 (Central European Standard Time)</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>43301</itunes:duration>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>This Is How They Tell Me the World Ends - The Cyberweapons Arms Race</title>
			<itunes:author>Nicole Perlroth</itunes:author>
			<itunes:subtitle></itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>Bloomsbury presents This Is How They Tell Me the World Ends by Nicole Perlroth, read by Allyson Ryan.

Zero day: a software bug that allows a hacker to break into your devices and move around undetected. One of the most coveted tools in a spy&#x27;s arsenal, a zero day has the power to silently spy on your iPhone, dismantle the safety controls at a chemical plant, alter an election and shut down the electric grid (just ask Ukraine).

For decades, under cover of classification levels and non-disclosure agreements, the United States government became the world’s dominant hoarder of zero days. US government agents paid top dollar - first thousands and later millions of dollars - to hackers willing to sell their lock-picking code and their silence.

Then the United States lost control of its hoard and the market.

Now those zero days are in the hands of hostile nations and mercenaries who do not care if your vote goes missing, your clean water is contaminated or our nuclear plants melt down.

Filled with spies, hackers, arms dealers and a few unsung heroes, written like a thriller and a reference, This Is How They Tell Me the World Ends is an astonishing feat of journalism. Based on years of reporting and hundreds of interviews, The New York Times reporter Nicole Perlroth lifts the curtain on a market in shadow, revealing the urgent threat faced by us all if we cannot bring the global cyber arms race to heel.</itunes:summary>
			<itunes:image href="https://am3pap003files.storage.live.com/y4mMa5UAdEYP3LsMQpxyQ8Y88ml0GAl-TWw_re44311g6WdA9BaYVBTKUHN1Cmn4W1kWPqOa3X_d-yLoA1pVxLyvihhShmYK4gilBTuazetUbO0p05GKpja9GvDlaIclj2Bj3p7sfyY3NP31QEqksxUaQCqN2hk1iAAkRQwFu6PBrn0nUEuSbrzL9v_Ll4Ur-NU?width=2000&amp;height=2000&amp;cropmode=none" />
			<enclosure url="https://onedrive.live.com/download?resid=3455FE3FC4C110A5%219457&amp;authkey=!AC28yJCGpSSbGTU&amp;filedisplay=track.m4a" length="1079821892" type="audio/mpeg"/>
			<pubDate>Thu Mar 24 2022 11:53:57 GMT+0100 (Central European Standard Time)</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>66208</itunes:duration>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Worm - The First Digital World War</title>
			<itunes:author>Mark Bowden</itunes:author>
			<itunes:subtitle></itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>Worm: The First Digital World War tells the story of the Conficker worm, a potentially devastating piece of malware that has baffled experts and infected more than twelve million computers worldwide. When Conficker was unleashed in November 2008, cybersecurity experts did not know what to make of it. Exploiting security flaws in Microsoft Windows, it grew at an astonishingly rapid rate, infecting millions of computers around the world within weeks. Once the worm infiltrated one system it was able to link it with others to form a single network under illicit outside control known as a “botnet.” This botnet was soon capable of overpowering any of the vital computer networks that control banking, telephones, energy flow, air traffic, health-care information — even the Internet itself. Was it a platform for criminal profit or a weapon controlled by a foreign power or dissident organization?

Surprisingly, the U.S. government was only vaguely aware of the threat that Conficker posed, and the task of mounting resistance to the worm fell to a disparate but gifted group of geeks, Internet entrepreneurs, and computer programmers. But when Conficker’s controllers became aware that their creation was encountering resistance, they began refining the worm’s code to make it more difficult to trace and more powerful, testing the Cabal lock’s unity and resolve. Will the Cabal lock down the worm before it is too late? Game on.</itunes:summary>
			<itunes:image href="https://am3pap003files.storage.live.com/y4mNWAqxw38hJmdDZ7LPZQZIqCcPxK9crHUFehBX0W8YIdThcHA-hAwjj7L-j79DbQ5mzIh9VYUpNy2rHkR55HOk9yKoJ6fYfrzfK5-IIjOJs1hpLjFh5BgtQP2PnQ73qGbZ3RE1Hg4m8xbIWiGVKODs7lijRDlUR3mA7PTMswg-krvFP6d250nPTSnnMhAma_A?width=2000&amp;height=2000&amp;cropmode=none" />
			<enclosure url="https://onedrive.live.com/download?resid=3455FE3FC4C110A5%219448&amp;authkey=!AGnYZQl1Vhzo1I0&amp;filedisplay=track.m4a" length="206222813" type="audio/mpeg"/>
			<pubDate>Thu Mar 24 2022 11:53:57 GMT+0100 (Central European Standard Time)</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>25737</itunes:duration>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Zero Day - A Jeff Aiken Novel</title>
			<itunes:author>Mark Russinovich</itunes:author>
			<itunes:subtitle></itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>A technothriller for the malware and Stuxnet era

An airliner’s controls abruptly fail mid-flight over the Atlantic. An oil tanker runs aground in Japan when its navigational system suddenly stops dead. Hospitals everywhere have to abandon their computer databases when patients die after being administered incorrect dosages of their medicine. In the Midwest, a nuclear power plant nearly becomes the next Chernobyl when its cooling systems malfunction.

At first, these random computer failures seem like unrelated events. But Jeff Aiken, a former government analyst who quit in disgust after witnessing the gross errors that led up to 9/11, thinks otherwise. Jeff fears a more serious cyber terrorism attack targeting the United States computer infrastructure is already under way. And as other menacing computer malfunctions pop up around the world, some with deadly results, he realizes that there isn’t much time if he hopes to prevent an international catastrophe.

Written by a global authority on cyber security, Zero Day presents a chilling “what if” scenario that, in a world completely reliant on technology, is more than possible today - it’s a cataclysmic disaster just waiting to happen.</itunes:summary>
			<itunes:image href="https://am3pap003files.storage.live.com/y4mNmcPoGPb86vi4MnbnCq3YWXfnvYFAuLGyAPlKz2FFtg2_oyHaDhzVmzz9Wm6IFZM6hl6up390eNUpEZZFr2CvhSeYv39AGmfZh_HoAv1-75sLOhX1SlXWpqtP23aA2Ql4wux5Ad5N6LbQ69RvcgxT1VfLxiejHwhsrstUKFvKauUR39EJ9NE2XAYnhhC5qkR?width=2000&amp;height=2000&amp;cropmode=none" />
			<enclosure url="https://onedrive.live.com/download?resid=3455FE3FC4C110A5%219450&amp;authkey=!AIvzWLllI1ivTpE&amp;filedisplay=track.m4a" length="592144785" type="audio/mpeg"/>
			<pubDate>Thu Mar 24 2022 11:53:57 GMT+0100 (Central European Standard Time)</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>34770</itunes:duration>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Algorithms to Live By - The Computer Science of Human Decisions</title>
			<itunes:author>Brian Christian and Thomas L. Griffiths</itunes:author>
			<itunes:subtitle></itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>A fascinating exploration of how computer algorithms can be applied to our everyday lives, helping to solve common decision-making problems and illuminate the workings of the human mind

All our lives are constrained by limited space and time, limits that give rise to a particular set of problems. What should we do, or leave undone, in a day or a lifetime? How much messiness should we accept? What balance of new activities and familiar favorites is the most fulfilling? These may seem like uniquely human quandaries, but they are not: computers, too, face the same constraints, so computer scientists have been grappling with their version of such problems for decades. And the solutions they've found have much to teach us.

In a dazzlingly interdisciplinary work, acclaimed author Brian Christian (who holds degrees in computer science, philosophy, and poetry, and works at the intersection of all three) and Tom Griffiths (a UC Berkeley professor of cognitive science and psychology) show how the simple, precise algorithms used by computers can also untangle very human questions. They explain how to have better hunches and when to leave things to chance, how to deal with overwhelming choices and how best to connect with others. From finding a spouse to finding a parking spot, from organizing one's inbox to understanding the workings of human memory, Algorithms to Live By transforms the wisdom of computer science into strategies for human living.</itunes:summary>
			<itunes:image href="https://am3pap003files.storage.live.com/y4mM05qpDIKrx8ehv5DWAtKoAgaFZNurvW_ryO9BVRKu7jvX4pT4jDojvSaSs6R70AFrqRzTnIuZe01pAvRzLl2CkQRhBRTG9qyYpZ-KVOvHAwhHIFORvV4U-Hqg7YfX-QnjVOSAy19HJJI8nZjL9nv2csFB6EpcNRbDaMg7G6-k549asSI5R7s9Q9reTYIvBWV?width=2400&amp;height=2400&amp;cropmode=none" />
			<enclosure url="https://onedrive.live.com/download?resid=3455FE3FC4C110A5%219486&amp;authkey=!AMqbI6h9jGTF6bw&amp;filedisplay=track.m4a" length="344117198" type="audio/mp4"/>
			<pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 08:30:57 GMT</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>42625</itunes:duration>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Never Split the Difference - Negotiating as if Your Life Depended on It</title>
			<itunes:author>Chris Voss</itunes:author>
			<itunes:subtitle></itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>A former international hostage negotiator for the FBI offers a new field-tested approach to high-stakes negotiations - whether in the boardroom or at home.

After a stint policing the rough streets of Kansas City, Missouri, Chris Voss joined the FBI, where his career as a hostage negotiator brought him face-to-face with a range of criminals, including bank robbers and terrorists. Reaching the pinnacle of his profession, he became the FBI's lead international kidnapping negotiator.

Never Split the Difference takes you inside the world of high-stakes negotiations and into Voss' head, revealing the skills that helped him and his colleagues succeed where it mattered most: in saving lives. In this practical guide, he shares the nine effective principles - counterintuitive tactics and strategies - you, too, can use to become more persuasive in both your professional and personal lives.

Life is a series of negotiations you should be prepared for: buying a car, negotiating a salary, buying a home, renegotiating rent, deliberating with your partner. Taking emotional intelligence and intuition to the next level, Never Split the Difference gives you the competitive edge in any discussion.</itunes:summary>
			<itunes:image href="https://am3pap003files.storage.live.com/y4mxsP4Lx2SuwRBcA6umN17X6-GJc3S8bsI1SUVSx3ZFUAhcbsf73txft6OVs9BKK-lVogY2XAhUIXqZkUIFML3uN-6UM55QbqcoanKmkKW_pVbsxz8kaJ859-f_dMXW19-A9r44-uDpntuDGaktifrOxutSRvKPVaLQHH0p60RIAfgbe8MxOC8whS87V5eBec-?width=3000&amp;height=3000&amp;cropmode=none" />
			<enclosure url="https://onedrive.live.com/download?resid=3455FE3FC4C110A5%219489&amp;authkey=!API83TuMQOSDPeg&amp;filedisplay=track.m4a" length="491266224" type="audio/mp4"/>
			<pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 12:35:28 GMT</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>29242</itunes:duration>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Skunk Works - A Personal Memoir of My Years at Lockheed</title>
			<itunes:author>Ben R. Rich</itunes:author>
			<itunes:subtitle></itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>This classic history of America's high-stakes quest to dominate the skies is "a gripping technothriller in which the technology is real" (New York Times Book Review).

 
From the development of the U-2 to the Stealth fighter, Skunk Works is the true story of America's most secret and successful aerospace operation. As recounted by Ben Rich, the operation's brilliant boss for nearly two decades, the chronicle of Lockheed's legendary Skunk Works is a drama of Cold War confrontations and Gulf War air combat, of extraordinary feats of engineering and human achievement against fantastic odds.
 

Here are up-close portraits of the maverick band of scientists and engineers who made the Skunk Works so renowned. Filled with telling personal anecdotes and high adventure, with narratives from the CIA and from Air Force pilots who flew the many classified, risky missions, this book is a riveting portrait of the most spectacular aviation triumphs of the twentieth century.</itunes:summary>
			<itunes:image href="https://am3pap003files.storage.live.com/y4mHc732mukqZXFyfVdxGHDVBNp4tNOKa9MXG1tQVRHdHksBBERZrETYAS10ch1W2b8AIHBz9Dq7ez1R45MHp0xMfbjBaSaWgg9yLySf3eqZowGbKcTLKZQ6ohuffWFKiivg6b1IRrazUGDDqLkCHWgV-MtNFvGCLycoJYOGNiW_xh_jjlB1ehsWd4xQkZz-F9X?width=2400&amp;height=2400&amp;cropmode=none" />
			<enclosure url="https://onedrive.live.com/download?resid=3455FE3FC4C110A5%219494&amp;authkey=!AHTlY20_3-ELpyc&amp;filedisplay=track.m4a" length="357338367" type="audio/mp4"/>
			<pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 13:30:27 GMT</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>43710</itunes:duration>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Social Engineering - The Science of Human Hacking</title>
			<itunes:author>Christopher Hadnagy</itunes:author>
			<itunes:subtitle></itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>Social Engineering: The Science of Human Hacking reveals the craftier side of the hacker's repertoire - why hack into something when you could just ask for access? Undetectable by firewalls and antivirus software, social engineering relies on human fault to gain access to sensitive spaces; in this book, renowned expert Christopher Hadnagy explains the most commonly used techniques that fool even the most robust security personnel and reveals how these techniques have been used in the past. 

The way that we make decisions as humans affects everything from our emotions to our security. Hackers, since the beginning of time, have figured out ways to exploit that decision making process and get you to take an action not in your best interest. Networks and systems can be hacked, but they can also be protected; when the "system" in question is a human being, there is no software to fall back on, no hardware upgrade, no code that can lock information down indefinitely. Human nature and emotion is the secret weapon of the malicious social engineering, and this book reveals how to recognize, predict, and prevent this type of manipulation by taking you inside the social engineer's bag of tricks.</itunes:summary>
			<itunes:image href="https://am3pap003files.storage.live.com/y4m2lfJRHQTVOE-McPCzBPlYFHnapQtX5FrIOBMJMROLwfV9RTQMQBlYY1Yo9X7wZ-0H-7QI_eNYC8NwKOiS5Zzu-ZVoKfbwVhOxWM42qPXVTY8i8YbQqWA3j0S5sz-UPe8zHF1CH-GFyjHl8v4nkidgKHmBXmVvJEmNEWWusVxdA9Daim7MLvJ_crc6jWlTIZI?width=2400&amp;height=2400&amp;cropmode=none" />
			<enclosure url="https://onedrive.live.com/download?resid=3455FE3FC4C110A5%219495&amp;authkey=!AA3bLWPrPePEXKs&amp;filedisplay=track.m4a" length="450412864" type="audio/mp4"/>
			<pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022 13:30:27 GMT</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>53604</itunes:duration>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>DarkMarket - CyberThieves, CyberCops and You</title>
			<itunes:author>Misha Glenny</itunes:author>
			<itunes:subtitle></itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>The benefits of living in a digital, globalised society are enormous; so too are the dangers. The world has become a law enforcer’s nightmare and every criminal’s dream. We bank online, shop online, date, learn, work and live online. But have the institutions that keep us safe on the streets learned to protect us in the burgeoning digital world? Have we become complacent about our personal security – sharing our thoughts, beliefs and the details of our daily lives with anyone who cares to relieve us of them?

In this fascinating and compelling book, Misha Glenny, author of the international best seller McMafia, explores the three fundamental threats facing us in the 21st century: cyber crime, cyber warfare and cyber industrial espionage. Governments and the private sector are losing billions of dollars each year, fighting an ever-morphing, often invisible, often super-smart new breed of criminal: the hacker.

Glenny has travelled and trawled the world. And by exploring the rise and fall of the criminal website, DarkMarket, he has uncovered the most vivid, alarming and illuminating stories. Whether JiLsi or Matrix, Iceman, Master Splynter or Lord Cyric; whether Detective Sergeant Chris Dawson in Scunthorpe or Agent Keith Mularski in Pittsburgh, Glenny has tracked down and interviewed all the players – the criminals, the geeks, the police, the security experts and the victims – and he places everyone and everything in a rich brew of politics, economics and history. The result is simply unputdownable.

DarkMarket is authoritative and completely engrossing. It’s a must-read for everyone who uses a computer: the essential crime book for our times.</itunes:summary>
			<itunes:image href="https://am3pap003files.storage.live.com/y4my-IkIMPrwN7hLXPHjnKQQiEKyODKpsURp-ITXP1XO4iyWRoPGgHlFmdMeo4x1o1xgTRuaBB3EmClSFdd_nI-mQq_TrnKGGTIPVV3sBbOiiuMcwdLhtBbqwz5uM0axg0EDdE9jg0Fe-I5ylgwpsASPm7bDQ6DlEbW1kC-xzVWJBpiAJBVMNbGkh-TxpoVbW6V?width=2850&amp;height=2850&amp;cropmode=none" />
			<enclosure url="https://onedrive.live.com/download?resid=3455FE3FC4C110A5%219497&amp;authkey=!ANcR_6rXqZzHYvI&amp;filedisplay=track.m4a" length="292013066" type="audio/mp4"/>
			<pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2022 14:13:34 GMT</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>33969</itunes:duration>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>We Are Legion (We Are Bob) (Bobiverse Book 1)</title>
			<itunes:author>Dennis Taylor</itunes:author>
			<itunes:subtitle></itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>Bob Johansson has just sold his software company and is looking forward to a life of leisure. There are places to go, books to read, and movies to watch. So it's a little unfair when he gets himself killed crossing the street.

Bob wakes up a century later to find that corpsicles have been declared to be without rights, and he is now the property of the state. He has been uploaded into computer hardware and is slated to be the controlling AI in an interstellar probe looking for habitable planets. The stakes are high: no less than the first claim to entire worlds. If he declines the honor, he'll be switched off, and they'll try again with someone else. If he accepts, he becomes a prime target. There are at least three other countries trying to get their own probes launched first, and they play dirty.

The safest place for Bob is in space, heading away from Earth at top speed. Or so he thinks. Because the universe is full of nasties, and trespassers make them mad - very mad.</itunes:summary>
			<itunes:image href="https://am3pap003files.storage.live.com/y4mu-d96CjoagkZEolArfGxYwtEFIRyEmC_GZghAVMZm2j-I4iYCwK6BPKA-CvMxuo91FOM989QX4glLl3l-nsHN18aUZNqUbEcsvNxBmAGCes174lCoZU1uk4V96dS-Qr9rapB2-8DPAc4hB63vFtotLh7COgezkKdVDBl4x2iefNOgf9S_DbOGbYO2W12tQKJ?width=2400&amp;height=2400&amp;cropmode=none" />
			<enclosure url="https://onedrive.live.com/download?resid=3455FE3FC4C110A5%219499&amp;authkey=!AKxW_P21XEb-4QU&amp;filedisplay=track.m4a" length="575843382" type="audio/mp4"/>
			<pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2022 14:52:02 GMT</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>34266</itunes:duration>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>For We Are Many (Bobiverse Book 2)</title>
			<itunes:author>Dennis Taylor</itunes:author>
			<itunes:subtitle></itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>Bob Johansson didn't believe in an afterlife, so waking up after being killed in a car accident was a shock. To add to the surprise, he is now a sentient computer and the controlling intelligence for a Von Neumann probe.

Bob and his copies have been spreading out from Earth for 40 years now, looking for habitable planets. But that's the only part of the plan that's still in one piece. A system-wide war has killed off 99.9% of the human race; nuclear winter is slowly making the Earth uninhabitable; a radical group wants to finish the job on the remnants of humanity; the Brazilian space probes are still out there, still trying to blow up the competition; And the Bobs have discovered a spacefaring species that sees all other life as food.

Bob left Earth anticipating a life of exploration and blissful solitude. Instead he's become a sky god to a primitive native species, the only hope for getting humanity to a new home, and possibly the only thing that can prevent every living thing in the local sphere from ending up as dinner.</itunes:summary>
			<itunes:image href="https://am3pap003files.storage.live.com/y4m7DukxjWqJzFPIt9CnBd1xPYgPptvYahwK8zohTSU1T3JvcjiL2Lnx3Ebt4X69JzUHEDTwMhVddX3JrDuK1A023itPGGY1QM8VJxyT9yHOT87G6f2m_DifzWsW1vp7Qgk65ggmgoEv-e7aZva3sj_BJ3dK6kvMq_ERW2-xeUOeTrgDHJa0e39bOlZgs5ibPKy?width=2400&amp;height=2400&amp;cropmode=none" />
			<enclosure url="https://onedrive.live.com/download?resid=3455FE3FC4C110A5%219501&amp;authkey=!APw-lm31CDnH1gs&amp;filedisplay=track.m4a" length="541646042" type="audio/mp4"/>
			<pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2022 14:53:02 GMT</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>32377</itunes:duration>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>All These Worlds (Bobiverse Book 3)</title>
			<itunes:author>Dennis Taylor</itunes:author>
			<itunes:subtitle></itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>Being a sentient spaceship really should be more fun. But after spreading out through space for almost a century, Bob and his clones just can't stay out of trouble.

They've created enough colonies so humanity shouldn't go extinct. But political squabbles have a bad habit of dying hard, and the Brazilian probes are still trying to take out the competition. And the Bobs have picked a fight with an older, more powerful species with a large appetite and a short temper.

Still stinging from getting their collective butts kicked in their first encounter with the Others, the Bobs now face the prospect of a decisive final battle to defend Earth and its colonies. But the Bobs are less disciplined than a herd of cats, and some of the younger copies are more concerned with their own local problems than defeating the Others.

Yet salvation may come from an unlikely source. A couple of eighth-generation Bobs have found something out in deep space. All it will take to save the Earth and perhaps all of humanity is for them to get it to Sol — unless the Others arrive first.</itunes:summary>
			<itunes:image href="https://am3pap003files.storage.live.com/y4mO_Q9AwLmt_RniOAu06P0DBh0aNHTqa0JU2t157uDSpwNkjdjvOmkm0QpNs6osVv9f_vSz3wXff6gVPCWxRiT-OaCGH2TixTp6exTga5Yl_EAmkc-va4rXWFjuLmM5MGskDJJd_k27FLFNeqvlpexp88HbrKdoWaS2RDMtO4aYhWCd37V8lGsc_gEPeVlyOoS?width=2400&amp;height=2400&amp;cropmode=none" />
			<enclosure url="https://onedrive.live.com/download?resid=3455FE3FC4C110A5%219503&amp;authkey=!ABW31rAyg-f_qdQ&amp;filedisplay=track.m4a" length="448147011" type="audio/mp4"/>
			<pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2022 14:53:02 GMT</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>28602</itunes:duration>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Turing's Cathedral - The Origins of the Digital Universe</title>
			<itunes:author>George Dyson</itunes:author>
			<itunes:subtitle></itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>In this revealing account of how the digital universe exploded in the aftermath of World War II, George Dyson illuminates the nature of digital computers, the lives of those who brought them into existence, and how code took over the world.
 
In the 1940s and ‘50s, a small group of men and women—led by John von Neumann—gathered in Princeton, New Jersey, to begin building one of the first computers to realize Alan Turing’s vision of a Universal Machine. The codes unleashed within this embryonic, 5-kilobyte universe—less memory than is allocated to displaying a single icon on a computer screen today—broke the distinction between numbers that mean things and numbers that do things, and our universe would never be the same. Turing’s Cathedral is the story of how the most constructive and most destructive of twentieth-century inventions—the digital computer and the hydrogen bomb—emerged at the same time.</itunes:summary>
			<itunes:image href="https://am3pap003files.storage.live.com/y4mj4jYVK441TEeYCzT-2y58oRl3DjiSFML4J6zV1T7T_qrJn9JyyIkOQEHATSCmGCumRQYDWu4vrxX8cAypOAH6Hq3SaCOnIPBAQ4PINv0Xv1MEE7VZCi8KoPfZgRqey58Ux9IRfVKIMcsG_ZDVdfECWahLfSDre-fUQ4xMm8FQtj_c2j2g4oyBJkEm94IK5Gy?width=1736&amp;height=1736&amp;cropmode=none" />
			<enclosure url="https://onedrive.live.com/download?resid=3455FE3FC4C110A5%219507&amp;authkey=!ACBeiLgWVXBQwmg&amp;filedisplay=track.m4a" length="328987080" type="audio/mp4"/>
			<pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 06:03:26 GMT</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>56443</itunes:duration>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Tracers in the Dark: The Global Hunt for the Crime Lords of Cryptocurrency</title>
			<itunes:author>Andy Greenberg</itunes:author>
			<itunes:subtitle></itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>From the award-winning author of Sandworm comes the propulsive story of a new breed of investigators who have cracked the Bitcoin blockchain, exposing once-anonymous realms of money, drugs, and violence. "Immensely readable... Greenberg takes readers on a romp through some of the most infamous dark web takedowns in recent memory.” (Washington Post)

Over the last decade, a single innovation has massively fueled digital black markets: cryptocurrency. Crime lords inhabiting lawless corners of the internet have operated more freely—whether in drug dealing, money laundering, or human trafficking—than their analog counterparts could have ever dreamed of. By transacting not in dollars or pounds but in currencies with anonymous ledgers, overseen by no government, beholden to no bankers, these black marketeers have sought to rob law enforcement of their chief method of cracking down on illicit finance: following the money.

But what if the centerpiece of this dark economy held a secret, fatal flaw? What if their currency wasn’t so cryptic after all? An investigator using the right mixture of technical wizardry, financial forensics, and old-fashioned persistence could uncover an entire world of wrongdoing.

Tracers in the Dark is a story of crime and pursuit unlike any other. With unprecedented access to the major players in federal law enforcement and private industry, veteran cybersecurity reporter Andy Greenberg tells an astonishing saga of criminal empires built and destroyed. He introduces an IRS agent with a defiant streak, a Bitcoin-tracing Danish entrepreneur, and a colorful ensemble of hardboiled agents and prosecutors as they delve deep into the crypto-underworld. The result is a thrilling, globe-spanning story of dirty cops, drug bazaars, trafficking rings, and the biggest takedown of an online narcotics market in the history of the Internet.

Utterly of our time, Tracers in the Dark is a cat-and-mouse story and a tale of a technological one-upmanship. Filled with canny maneuvering and shocking twists, it answers a provocative question: How would some of the world’s most brazen criminals behave if they were sure they could never get caught?</itunes:summary>
			<itunes:image href="https://link.storjshare.io/raw/juxi33aa4exo7ceznkk3du3b23ja/storage/Audiobooks/Tracers%20in%20the%20Dark.jpg" />
			<enclosure url="https://link.storjshare.io/raw/jvqsypyynohtdtt43nh2mks2ajba/storage/Audiobooks/Tracers%20in%20the%20Dark.m4b" length="619077777" type="audio/mp4"/>
			<pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2022 06:03:26 GMT</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>38804</itunes:duration>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>This Machine Kills Secrets: How Wikileakers, Cypherpunks, and Hacktivists Aim to Free the World's Information</title>
			<itunes:author>Andy Greenberg</itunes:author>
			<itunes:subtitle></itunes:subtitle>
			<itunes:summary>The machine that kills secrets is a powerful cryptographic code that hides the identities of leakers and hacktivists as they spill the private files of government agencies and corporations bringing us into a new age of whistle blowing. With unrivaled access to figures like Julian Assange, Daniel Domscheit-Berg, and Jacob Applebaum, investigative journalist Andy Greenberg unveils the group that brought the world WikiLeaks, OpenLeaks, and BalkanLeaks.

This powerful technology has been evolving for decades in the hands of hackers and radical activists, from the libertarian enclaves of Northern California to Berlin to the Balkans. And the secret-killing machine continues to evolve beyond WikiLeaks, as a movement of hacktivists aims to obliterate the world's institutional secrecy. Never have the seemingly powerless had so much power to disembowel big corporations and big government.</itunes:summary>
			<itunes:image href="https://link.storjshare.io/raw/jxkciskcrwwillismgmo2el34o2a/storage/Audiobooks/This%20Machine%20Kills%20Secrets.jpg" />
			<enclosure url="https://link.storjshare.io/raw/jvnprso7bm5snrwpxgens7vrp5lq/storage/Audiobooks/This%20Machine%20Kills%20Secrets.m4b" length="373303055" type="audio/mp4"/>
			<pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2022 06:03:26 GMT</pubDate>
			<itunes:duration>46076</itunes:duration>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
